Tell me how you think I'm wrong, when I say I feel so lost
Tell me why you think you're love, erase all that it cost
Tell me why you look at me, like I'm just a piece of dust
Tell me how you think you know, when I give away my trust
out for show star shine is so bright watch the secrets unfold
What's this working right now?
Okay, I have some good news though, but I did I was
Miraculously someone didn't buy it from under me like I'm way too long to buy it. I did I
Should have like bought it right away, but I bought the domain
for psyche awakens of I was really trying to like, you know, I wanted to do like a more custom website
Even if I had to put a link tree up there that'd be still be good because I have a lot of links, you know
But then link tree is like 20 bucks a month and I'm like
It's basically I know a little bit about web programming and like making a web page and stuff like that
And that's for like a page of links. I mean I can create a page of links
Just myself like easily without you know for free
So even the link tree is like, you know, we're at recognizable name and it's pretty cool for people that don't know anything about
Programming and a bunch of links and stuff. It's really good for some people and I have a link. I don't even think I have one
But I but basically I found another alternative is called
chirp
It's makes it really easy to
Basically, you know
Have a link tree type. What's that? But it's even pull the links great thing you guys can check it out psycheawakens.com
It's up right now
And I I mean I like it I like it a lot and customize a little bit. I mean I still have a lot of work to do on it
I'm gonna add my store there. I'm gonna put more more design merch
I know it's like you know merch is like, you know, not a big selling thing anyway, but it's nice to have merch up
And I know just I mean I'll eventually buy something, but you're sure I can get
I think actually I have cool logos and stuff. I think I have some cool graphic design. I hardly pull cart
Yeah, okay, so I just need I just want to make sure like guys
Like there's certain people that are just criticizing for like they're not they're not offering any kind of
Value to the conversation all they're doing is criticizing. Oh, you don't do this. You don't do this like they don't understand
I have a tiktok site where I do all tarot. I so it's like this person just ignorant
You know, they obviously not a big watcher of the show. They're just gonna criticize some mods
If you see someone like that you can just come
You can just, you can just time him out, but I mean, I'll end up, I'm going to end up kicking some of these people out, because I've had enough of it really, and then it's like, and people like Arthur, Arthur begging to be mod, I never let him, I mean, I took him off the mod ship, right?
There was like 50 people last night 55 people 60 people last night. So goodbye
Let's see. Yeah, it's too late. Yeah, too late too late for you
Bye
I don't care if you're a number three chatter or whatever.
I don't want people putting this misinformation out about me.
Because then, so it was on Beat The Show.
I'm not going to blame Beat about anything.
I'm just going to leave her name out of it.
Arthur called in.
I mean, she did laugh.
And she was like, oh, it's because he's charging.
People look up on the panel.
Oh, he's charged Sam Antenna.
I've never charged Sam Antenna.
I've maybe I don't think I've ever even charged anything to come on the panel. I do charge
Sometimes to sponsor an open panel. It's not really that typical. It's in the description of the show
I usually don't even do it. I usually was just like, you know, open it eventually
But you know, sometimes I do like to have a it's so it's like, oh, oh, they're sitting there laughing
Oh, well, here's don't play me for saying anything about you. Well, it's like you're sitting there laughing too along with everybody
Um, criticize me when you think I'm not there when I'm sitting right there listening like just basically it's sitting right there
Like I you have a lot of times my name always gets brought up. I I wasn't
I didn't bring up anybody's name
Okay, so yeah, there's people like this. Uh, yeah, the too late is gone, right?
It's too late gone or did you start another account if he's gone? Okay. Yeah, I don't want that person here
call me limp wrist they're saying oh
Yeah, you can just hide people like that Moz. You can be more proactive about hiding people just like if somebody's a regular here
No, it's getting me down
It's just like it's just constant
It's like it's been constant like this for months and that's what kind of hurts the show is that people say oh
There's nobody over there. It's just like that kind of image and no one's saying well
No, he has a good show. So does anybody know this was my top financial month on the show? It might be a slow month
But it's like, if it was my best financial month,
do you think I'm like sad right now?
Do you think I care if there's 20 people or 50 people
as long as you know, I don't know.
It's not about quantity, it's about quality.
There could be a hundred people
that have a hundred assholes.
You can have like five people and have five true friends.
Do you prefer a hundred assholes in your life
or five true friends?
Let me know.
There's a hundred of those assholes. I mean, there's a million asshole a billion assholes in the world
You're gonna be you know, let them all in your life to run ramp it, right? It's like there's a lot of assholes
There's like very few true friends. That's what I'm actually looking for is like
Good people quality people people that support the show, right?
It's like not like a bunch of assholes. We are there to troll and then once that once you know
My show's channel is taken down or whatever whatever they're trying to do
There's going to the next one and it's taking some kind of fun like a little game for them
They didn't know like they're coming up against me. It's not gonna be like so easy
Because first of all, I'll fight. Okay. I'm a fight. I'll fight especially for my for my rights and like my show and things like that
I will fight for that stuff, right?
And second of all, I'm just not easy to take down.
I have a lot of protection.
I mean, if people haven't figured it out yet,
it's like I would have been down right now.
There's people that are a lot more successful than me,
that have had their shows and channels taken down
for a lot less happening and things like that, right?
So it's like, I've been really fortunate actually.
I've been really fortunate.
For someone has been this person someone that's been porn bombs a hundred times
Let's see. I was drunk last night. I was but by Tony. I was drunk last night. I'm not gonna
Deny that right I was drunk am I allowed to be drunk guys? Yeah, I'm not an alcohol is a drug, right? I
Was drunk and I was in a bad mood, but I was also
The acting a little bit like I put on this song I do like did you ever hear the song here's a song
Psyche is awake and unhappy, it shows In his American flag speedos
Laying back smiling, snacking on flames Flamin' hot Cheetos, drownin' old pain
Bita and the rest
Left him behind
Thought they knew best
Now he's stuck musin'
With a soul full of ache
Lookin' like art
But his heart's gonna break
Always the nice one
Handsome and true
Didn't deserve what the trolls put him through
But he wasn't their victim
Oh no, not at all
He was their father
Bruises and all
Chat forgive me
I didn't confess
The truth's a bit messy
Those moves
I ain't the fool that you thought you could school
I'm the one who built the stage where you had to cruel
And if I didn't love you, I'd tear it all down
But instead I just
Just make it loud
Your daddy's still smiling
Damn, he's proud
Psyche's awake in his patriotic blues left behind
So the fire he refuses to lose, flame in hot heart, in these red white and bruised.
Oh.
That's a pretty song.
I mean, I think that's a good song.
Do you like it?
I like it.
It's pretty.
Day by new shirt, too
This is I guess this is the teeth and face of like, you know, somebody that's on a lot of drugs, right?
Sure, okay guys. Hi, you like that
I'm back.
How flashed in this morning that he ran me off on YouTube?
How flashed is pretty much the dumbest person
I've ever encountered on YouTube.
I think he's the dumbest.
I mean, he was like this weird personality,
a kind of zany kind of thing, like a captain kangaroo,
real Yankovic almost personality.
And I didn't find him particularly interesting
or as chic funny at all.
And then he came on the show one night and he put some kind of, like, Nickelodeon, you know, with a god Dan, Dan something, there's some god from Nickelodeon that was, like, you know, some TDS stuff.
He put some kind of, like, CP, actual CP or something as a porn bomb in my shows.
That is that you know see you porn bomb me is like I don't really care that kind of that's just like disgusting or really that is like
Not only
You know morally a hortley everything's wrong about it
they're putting that you mean possessing that kind of thing to be able to try to play down somebody's show but
Just to do that that's pretty much the word as low as you can go and so I consider him the scale of the earth and
I don't care what he says. He also was on, you know, Vita's show right after that saying,
oh, I'm, I took Psyche down. Like, you know, he doesn't, he doesn't understand like a porn bomb.
It's like, I can, you know, just delete it. It's like, not gonna, people think that, you know,
I've been porn bombed over a hundred times. Is my channel still here? Oh yeah, that too.
Hey, Spunky, how are you? I've been porn bombed over a hundred times. Is my channel still here?
Yes. Has the, has porn bombing taken down channels? Yes.
But it's like usually it's an inexperienced people that haven't encountered the idea that people will do that
And so it's good my show actually kind of brings awareness to that it can be done
It's gonna be done be the two like it can be done to people, but it's like it can be
Del with you know, you can deal with it. It's not gonna be the end of the thing
You can deal with most stuff on YouTube. I don't know Arthur. I'm about to ban you because you because Arthur what you did with Arthur is like
This morning. What's wrong with my psyche showed I have no people. I was sitting right there
I know it was like you brought my name up out of the blue, right?
And it's like it's not that it's like maybe it was even sure like you're in the chatter 16 people there
I mean there's yeah, there's two people right now, whatever
That why are you are you so concerned about my numbers Arthur like why are you concerned about my numbers and I like I said
It was my best financial month on YouTube. It was my first month of making for four digits as a YouTube creator
Okay, I just that's not even considering cash apps. That's just on YouTube alone. Okay on YouTube through the YouTube
Respondentation on four figures, right? It's my first month of that
So am I gonna be saying oh no?
Yeah, do I care how many people are in the chat as long as people are watching? I'll be right back guys play the way
Hold on that's something I have to do something real quick. I think it's about there
But I'll try to put on slip or something
Do I have any more like I'll play a couple of these
Who the fuck do you think you are you're trying to like talk to me like what I?
Can't be with a skinny bitch. I've been with a fucking bottle like
Growing up, I don't give a fuck about
size zero I
Enjoy fat bitches
I didn't say I didn't say you know I just thought it was I thought the story was shot
Like you put it a very very very like you think that I can't get with fucking like I never said any
I consider good-looking bitches. It's like shut the fuck up. You're nobody like
You can look at me. You can see I look way better than any of you motherfuckers
Well, I don't think it's not here. It's not shit compared to me
Just because I like a fucking
Hey, what I could take your bitch like any fucking bitch that any of these losers that have I've taken I
Don't walk them
I love fat bitches, it's not so hard to understand, you're so fucking stupid, you can't understand that a guy likes a fat bitch, urgh, fucking retard, lady, you're a weirdo, yeah, pedophile, gonna die one day.
Fuck holy shit, there's no water. Oh my god
No, I'm gonna die one day. Sorry. I didn't mean to die in your screen. You'll help my ratings good. I'm sorry. I'm died
I did I didn't die
Man, what are you doing?
I'm sitting here looking at you in a state of shock
Uh, that's right. What? In a state of shock is watching you. Why did you see your discord?
You're just on my discord? Oh, no, I made a discord. I didn't even remember. Remember when you
Then I asked you for nude, so for your nude photos and he sent me a picture of South Park.
South Park, yeah.
Lemmy Weeks, the gerbil from South Park, yeah.
That wasn't a, that wasn't a nude photo.
Yeah, that was a good one.
That wasn't a good, it wasn't, I know that was a good episode, but it didn't make any sense for what I asked,
and then he sent me a picture of a giant cartoon gerbil.
He asked for nudes, and so I just see that in the side of my asshole.
Oh my god.
So
I was hoping that wasn't the joke
Hold on
You have motherfuckers that are attacking me
No, it's attacking you
Some dumbass questions. What's on that? Oh, this is your brother is chef
So I was attacking you is that I is your brother is chef
They said your brother's a chef
Every attack someone said your brother is a chef. Oh
My god, these are funny
Hold on no, I'm trying to put I have some downloaded already. I don't want to like take it too long bit
There's like two or three laughs and see
I just played these ones yesterday you guys are enjoying these
Um, yeah, I got this there's a program called opus. Um, that will basically, you know, go through your video and buying like the funniest moments somehow. I don't know how I does it that then it puts them together.
I really enjoyed it. Um.
Yeah, this just takes a second to upload some of these.
I just have a couple more left.
Choose files.
Two more.
Do you guys like those?
I think they're pretty funny.
Okay, it don't mean shit.
Oh god, so I don't know like, you know, you know, I had a problem with my bike yesterday, of course
And I was like all freaked out about that and then
You know I
Got kicked out of this they can't come back to the store. Well, they just like one of the guys that I don't think he's the owner though
I'd actually know the owner so I
Think I'll be okay, but there's anything download nothing download. Well, anyway, it's fine. Are we guys doing?
The high is so pickled. Yeah
Hold on. Hey, there's bunkie. What'd you say you're inspired by somebody? I'm doing okay. It's just like
By eating today, no, I just woke up actually. Oh, here we go. Hey, he's still just ever clear. Sorry, man
I do not drink ever clear. I have never checked ever clear in my life. Are you interested in that size?
I need that booty that's bigger than me. Oh my god
Bigger than you it's a triple. Oh, it's ours triple F
Like this one. Yeah, I like this booty. I need this booty separate
It's ever bigger. That sounds like it's something. It's too big
Yeah, and I and I hope she's comfortable with me sticking my face in it
You know the booty thing
Okay, I'm gonna stick your face in it. Yeah. Okay. You should see well
There's an episode of my 600 pound life and the guy has a girlfriend and she's like, you know
He's 600 pounds
So so he has to take her on the he has to take her on the porch
He takes her outside on the porch and he hoses her down with the hook
That's the only way he can wash her he has to this hose her down that she's like bending over and he's like spraying her
Spraying her butt clean. Have you ever seen that episode? Hey, man, whatever it takes
Would you do that for your girlfriend?
Whatever it takes. Also, there was another episode
where this woman was dating a guy and
She had him
I'll use my tongue. Oh god. No, this thing would have they would have him like wipe her with the
Like he had a what you wiped her in the bath if he like came in and wiped her because she didn't wipe very well. Oh
My god. Yeah, so these are some of the classic moments
I'm at the store the store. I was like, you know, I I bought that the
via psyche awakens domain, I think and I and I thought it was gonna be like, you know
usually they charge the next day and so I get that I get to clean up my account and
And so I thought I had like ten bucks extra and so I brought like six dollars cash and like that
And I had ten dollars on my card
So I get six dollars cash, but then the car kept getting declined because it was like, you know empty
And I didn't have any like way to pay and so I was just like oh just take this off take this off
And he's like I can't do it. I can't do it. I was like well you can't he's like because I paid cash
He was having he was confused how to like
Boyd the transaction, but he was like taking other customers. So it's a boy
It was just it's just a matter of like writing down, you know for the person that that balances out the register
Oh, it might be like this. You know, there's like this what has had to be cancelled or something like this
Transaction, it's not a big deal, but he kept saying oh, it can't be dead
He's a gold year. He said go bring the money go bring the money and I was like, I don't have it
And I was like, and I wouldn't leave until he gave me like a cigar and the drink and I'm like, I'll pay you back the dollar like I was off big tomorrow.
I'm there every day practically buying stuff. And he's like, he's like, you can't come back here.
And that he is not the owner of the store. He's like a guy that works there. I know the ladies that work there.
And I know like the guy that owns it. And so I don't think that they have a problem because I'm there all the time. It's a little mom and pop store.
So I don't know.
So anyway that happened and so then I was in a bad mood and then like people came in here sort of harassing me
Like you know like usual and I just like didn't I didn't I didn't feel like dealing with it and the
Yeah, so I mean
And I do yeah, and then people are like, well, you get donations like why didn't you have money?
Yeah, I do get donations, but it's like the super chats don't I don't get those instantly. Okay, so the super chats
Come through what if you know about anything on YouTube they come through once a month, right? So
So it's like, you know, I can I can I get
Donations of stuff. It doesn't mean that I have that money if you spend, okay, but I'll be okay today
I'm just like waiting on something right now
Let me check on it.
Let me do a couple of text messages.
We'll see how it goes.
I am kind of hungry now, so I'm ready for food.
What is today?
Oh, it's actually my favorite day at Subway.
It's like the tuna sandwich.
The way they make it for me, I do basically a tuna melt.
I put the tuna, I put like a couple like, you know, mayonnaise and mustard, oil or vinegar,
and maybe onions and maybe something else, maybe peppers.
And it's a really good, then it's really good tuna melon. It's a warm, it's really good.
I'm craving that right now. Let me check my messages.
Anyway guys, what do you if you guys go check go to go just go look at the and if you haven't seen it
I think probably people have seen it but just go psycheawakens.com see if it's up and working and if you like
You'd like what you see so far, you know, I'll put I'll like update the graphics
And stuff like that hi Athens
Do not let Athens on the piano why not I like Athens
Hey, thank you. Look, there's a piece of member for one month. Hold on. What's this? He owns my boy. Are you boy? Oh my gosh
If he says a member for one month, unfortunately, unfortunately, I hate to ban members, but I hate banning members
I really do I like master computer doesn't own shit. He doesn't own me or nor anybody else
he's like a little follower and
You're obviously one of his little followers which makes you even less
Vinny thing, so I'm just gonna go ahead and
Sorry to ban members but I adhesive
Yeah, bye. Yeah, he does
So yeah, anybody that comes in harassing me. I'm just gonna be hiding from now on
So you really it's like really easy now because it's like it used to be like
Oh, are they they were maybe they're just expressing in their opinion about something or maybe they're like, you know
Just to troll naturally. Yeah, if you come fuck with me, I'm just gonna kick you off
This is ban you all ban you straight out like the mods will the mods. I just want mods to time out people
Yeah, Athens. Well, I don't know why Athens not Athens was a good mod
Ilya, I mean Ilya
I mean if you ever perform by me again, I
Won't I won't forgive you. Okay. I won't if you ever perform by me again, Ilya
I'm just gonna ban you okay
But otherwise, you know how I give people chances the second chances and I like to give people second chances
Okay, let's see
Let me get everybody that should let me know if I you know, you think you should be on the
As a mod okay, let me know if you think you should but anyway
Yeah mods, I don't want you to hide hide anybody just time them out and let me know if like this person's like saying shit
Like if I miss did I make a mess unbent? No, I'm not doing a mess unbent because
I like if you look at my ban list it's all like most of the names are doxing or they're like
About somebody else or they're actually dox names or I mean it's like there's not like
Oh, there's it's not like really a question of like should they be banned or not like everybody has uh
Mermaid you'd like a you'd like a mod okay
Hi title ban hold on let's check it out
I mean i'm not i'm a nice person it's like if you're nice to me
I will give you second chances, I mean, it's like,
really, I will give people another chance.
But, okay, I think I got everybody now.
That should be, but you know, it's like I really need,
like I've had problems with mods
from doing kind of the same thing,
but it's like now I know people more and better, right?
And so I trust the people that are here,
But guys, like, no, like, if you're a mod and you start hiding people, then, like, other mods will tell me.
If you're a mod and you start taking out personal bandettas, other mods will tell me, and I can't have that, okay?
Yeah, thank you. So, Sassy knows. Sassy's been a mod from the beginning. Jamie's a mod from the beginning.
I mean, Jamie doesn't even, I don't think, I don't think Jamie knows how to hide people. It's okay. It's okay. I love Jamie.
You know, Jamie's like a top mod.
I don't want her to like have to hide people.
She does that a timeout, right?
At least she knows how to hide people.
But she, I mean, I would allow her to if she wanted to, right?
She's, you know, in my top mods.
But you think of sexy or what, I shave every day?
Well, I may shave.
I just woke up though.
I'm just waiting on some things.
I'm gonna go try to,
I'm gonna go back to the liquor store and,
I'm gonna be I'm gonna pay them the dollar like that, you know, they front of me a dollar basically
I'm gonna pay the dollar apologize and say it was it was an accident and it wasn't like intentional the guy just got so
Mad at me sometimes and not to say anything about any race or anything
The guy the guy was Asian and he'd like, you know, sometimes Asian and I love it. I love all Asian
You know, you know, whatever country my sister-in-law's Chinese, you know
Chinese Japanese Vietnamese Filipino. I love Asian people
But I've had some issues with shopkeepers before like I've like where it's like with those kind of things
They've they get really mad at me and stuff like I mean some of them have I don't want to be stereotypical or anything
You know that's what happens
Like that, I don't know or might be like it may be like that or I don't know if I want to program though
But I know this one is I
Don't think subscribers so it should be
It should be, I don't know if that is a nightbot working.
I don't see the nightbot coming.
Oh, here it goes.
Yeah, it's coming through.
Yeah, I don't know if subscribe is up.
I need to have the program in the subscribe command.
I don't know, I don't have that yet.
Thank you, Sassy knows them.
And if you go like this,
I think this will show up the commands too.
It will like, put a link to where,
or maybe it's command, I'm not sure.
Oh, there it goes, yeah.
The bot commands are available there,
program commands for the show, but I'm gonna like put some I found out a way on chat
GPT is just what still walking me through how to do it, but there's some ways they
can do some other cool stuff on the show like I'm
I can put like fortune and it will like I can put like lists and I'll put people on a list
I'll keep it like fortune and it will like give like a general like, you know oracle to or whatever
Yeah, we're almost yeah, I'm almost up to me that 3,000 subs
I mean, it's like people that criticized me. It's like first of all, I put a lot of work in the show
They're like, oh, this is not work. They're not doing anything. You're sitting there talking to the camera
That's easy and it's like well if it's easy like why isn't everybody doing it not everybody's doing it a lot of people are on YouTube
It seems like everybody's on YouTube, but not a lot not everybody's on YouTube. Most people have no content
Then there's people with some content. That's how I started just a little bit of content a few videos
Bad quality you know bad quality videos, right?
The first ones like I have a minor or a terrible level of mine privated and then
I started my bad quality lives, which is like, you know, I had, I did some bad lives, you know, probably as like, you know
And I think they're probably like gonna be charming if I look back at them
But Miser said they're cringy and like, you know, other people were saying like, oh, you know
He's got your shows got so much better or whatever
So I had most of the beginning episodes privated
But then now I put in the link. Yeah. Yeah, I had my best month on YouTube this month
And also people say oh, oh my god, you know your um your your ship is down guys half a million
This year half a million
Minutes watch half a million. I never thought I'd be like a half a million anything on YouTube half a million minutes
Of my show watch okay half a million
500 something thousand or 487 thousand, but then there's even more because I have so many things private
They don't log that those minutes when they consider that so I can maybe get to a million minutes
I don't know. Maybe I have had a million minutes with all my shows combined
I think I probably have because I only have about half of them half of them. Um, I'm private it
Okay, so I'm doing good
But now I'm getting a little moody
because I'm getting hungry and stuff
and I'm waiting on something.
And so I'm probably just gonna end until I eat.
Or maybe go take a nap or something while I wait.
And I'd love you guys, thank you for being here.
I just wanted to announce I have the new Psyche Awakens
website up.
It's not like any, I mean, I don't,
I will eventually will do some,
like I'll put a schedule out there
if anyone wants to like, you know,
schedule readings and stuff like that.
I'll put a calendar up and stuff.
You know, you can actually book the time and do the official booking the cash up is up there, too
I'm gonna put my merch store there. I'm gonna put my link to my YouTube channel my links to my tiktok
I'm gonna get the Kickstarter done
I'll look into the Kickstarter for the for the tarot deck. I have a lot of interesting things happening
I might do a Kickstarter for the book, but that's probably gonna be after the kicks
I'm gonna do one at a time. So I'll do the tarot deck first
Because I think I'd be good to have a chapter of the book with some of the tarot cards and you know to kind of kind of like do a
promote the deck with the book after the book kind of thing. I don't want to do it before because then
If I you know if I have delays or something like that. I don't want people. Oh, where is he said you're gonna do a book?
I'm gonna do the book the books already outlines
It's gonna be about 500 pages
And I'll have a special hardcover probably for those certain people and then
You know, I might sell it through Etsy or you know, Amazon and stuff and then eventually
In mass market paperback, but we'll see we'll see how it goes
But I love you guys. I'll be back for you
Maybe have some coffee or something, but I'll see you soon. Wow